Hello friends, meet me again
Asep, a life insurance agent at mone
lifeif Indonesia. On this occasion,
I will discuss one of the newest insurance products
from manif Indonesia
called mdla Man lifeif Dynamic Life
assurance. This product was launched in
April
2024, so it's only been a month. From this video
I made, this is a
very unique life insurance product and
maybe it's the first time it's been in
Indonesia. In the past, we knew what was
called i jiwa, there was a term Life, there was
H Life for
life, there was endomen, E Duwi guna,
and there was a unit link. Well, if
this product is one product, it can be three
products at once, it can be th Life, it
can be H Life, it can even be
endomen, only unitlink, yes, which can't be
because this is not a unitlink
but traditional life insurance, so the
old understanding of the various types of
insurance is completely overhauled here
because one product can be three types of
products. Let's see, the product information
I have displayed on my blog
asuransihijau.com You can find it
on the traditional life insurance product page,
then just click on manuif Dynamic Life
assurance.
Well, here it is
mdla, this mdla has a tagline, free to choose.
What is it like?  Well, I just read it, mdla
or manual lifeif Dynamic Life
assurance is a life insurance product
with flexible final benefits and coverage period.
This product was launched in April
2024. mdla is classified as traditional life insurance. It
can be a term life
insurance or term life insurance. H Life or
life source life insurance or
more useful endowments depending on the plan and
coverage period chosen. mdla
can be used for the purpose of
income protection, debt protection,
inheritance preparation, pension funds or wealth accumulation. The
superior features are free to choose the
coverage period between 20 to 90 years
so that it can be adjusted to your
needs. Free to determine the benefits. At the end of the
coverage period, there is a choice of whether
without cash value, the premium is returned 100%
or up to
100% liquid.  then free to set the
premium payment period can be 5 years 10 years
15 20 or Pay continuously cash value benefits
for plans that provide
cash value is guaranteed safe not
affected by market fluctuations yes because
this is traditional life insurance
insurance benefits we
see mdla consists of three plans that
can be selected as follows plan a
plan B and plan C for
death benefits All are the same yes that is
100% up if the up is R billion then the disbursement is
R billion now the difference is the
End of Coverage Period benefit for
plan A there is no End of Coverage Period benefit
aka the premium is forfeited yes
plan B the premium is returned 100%
then plan C the up is disbursed 100%.
then the coverage period for plan A
there is a choice between 20 or 30 years
for plan B there are more choices
20 30 40 50 to 60 years plan C has
more choices 20 to
90 years and all of these have a maximum,
namely Until the age of the insured 110 years
Okay, please read the information here,
then I will discuss the
general provisions of the product name mdla manualif
Dynamic Life assurance type of
traditional life insurance product can be
tem Life hal Life or used in
Rupiah currency there are two insurance benefits, yes one
death benefit is 100% up
during the coverage period two benefits
End of coverage period, namely plan A
without cash value plan B 100% premium and
plan C 100% up the insured's entry age 30
days to 70 years the policyholder's entry age is
at least 18
years the coverage period plan A 20 or
30 years plan B 20 to 60 years plan
C 20 to 90 years maximum up
to the insured's age of 110 years the
premium payment period there are 5 choices  10 15 20
or during the insurance period the
premium payment frequency can be annual, semi-annual,
quarterly or monthly, the minimum premium
for annual premiums is R5 million per
year, semi-annual 2.625 million, quarterly
1.375 million and monthly
r75,000 per month, minimum up to r00 million,
maximum according to the under rating decision,
so it can be R billion, R billion 10 billion
or even more. Yes, please
just submit a grace period or new period of 45
days from the due date or from the date of
policy selection, policy review period
or free look period of 14 days from the
date the policy is received, the
underrating method is full
underrating, there are complete health questions
and it is possible to limit
medical tests if necessary, the premium payment method
can be transferred, autod debate, savings
or autod debate, credit card for
monthly and or quarterly premium payments,
it must be autod debit, yes, the
next thing you need to know is that
this exception is standard, yes, for
life insurance in general, in manualif,
suicide in the first 2 years, the insured is
or as a result of
committing a crime, the insured is
undergoing execution, the death penalty by the
court, four occurs as a result of a
crime or murder committed
by an interested party in
dependent for example by the heirs
yes sorry yes five
other exceptions listed in the
special provisions if there are these special provisions
please
read next standard claim method
also yes here there is a death claim
please read and there is also an
End of Coverage Period claim
for plan b or c yes next how to
register fill out the SPJ or
life insurance application letter with a
photocopy of KTP proposal illustration proof of
transfer of premium payments and
other supporting documents if needed
such as photocopy of credit card or
savings book medical documents if there is a history of
illness or financial quisioner if the Upay
taken is very high Next
If you are interested in getting an
illustration of this product please fill out
the form include name gender
date of birth occupation smoking or
not marital status location
mobile number email and height weight
and so on yes the data is like this
then the selected plan premium payment period sum
insured frequency of
premium payments and premium payment method
then include an additional message yes
If you want a
specific request below there is an mdla brochure
and reply mdla please download this
is a source from Man directly
Okay that's the information that I can
convey briefly about the
mdla manualif Dynamic Life
assurance product hopefully it will be useful for those of you
who are looking for life insurance either
for income protection purposes
maybe you are a breadwinner or
debt protection maybe  Do you have
business debt or any debt that needs to be
protected so that it does not burden
your heirs if something happens or
for inheritance or for
wealth accumulation or for retirement funds? You
can all get an illustration of
this product or a consultation. Yes, please
contact me directly either
via WA or the comments column
below. Thank you for your attention. I
apologize for any shortcomings. May
we all be healthy and prosperous always,
amen.